{"tokens": ["▁contact", "s", "▁in", "▁Paris", "▁France"], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-GPE", "B-GPE"], "spans": ["None", "None", "None", "Paris", "France"]}
{"tokens": ["▁account", "▁with", "▁rev", "▁>", "▁$", "1", "m", "▁and", "▁state", "▁is", "▁NY"], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MONEY", "I-MONEY", "I-MONEY", "I-MONEY", "O", "O", "O", "B-GPE"], "spans": ["None", "None", "None", "> $1m", "> $1m", "> $1m", "> $1m", "None", "None", "None", "NY"]}
{"tokens": ["▁customers", "▁with", "▁an", "▁annual", "▁income", "▁of", "▁$", "100", ",", "0"], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "B-MONEY", "I-MONEY", "I-MONEY"], "spans": ["None", "None", "None", "annual", "None", "None", "None", "100,0", "100,0", "100,0"]}
{"tokens": ["▁mi", "ke", "▁is", "▁assistant", "▁to", "▁which", "▁listed", "▁customer", "▁who", "▁graduated", "▁mit", "?"], "labels": ["B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "spans": ["mike", "mike", "None", "None", "None", "None", "None", "None", "None", "None", "None", "None"]}
